Sreejith R

PROFILE INFO

3D Generalist & AI-AR/VR Developer

**** +91 88381 90703

shrsree341o@gmail.com

No:40/9,6th street(ext), Gandhipuram, Coimbatore- 641012



https://sreejithshr.github.io/

ABOUT ME

With over 4 years of experience in computer graphics designing and development, I possess the skills to design intricate 3D elements, and developing immersive experiences through AR & VR. Proficient in both independent and collaborative work environments, I am dedicated to achieving visual excellence and creativity. Additionally, my expertise extends to Al, LLM, Diffusers and chatbot development, enabling me to integrate advanced technologies into AR/VR Development for interactivity enhanced and Immersive experience.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Python
- Next.js
- Langchain
- Unreal Engine
- Game Development
- Generative AI & Machine learning

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Blender
- Unreal Engine
- Multi-model AI
- AR/VR Application Development
- **Product Management**
- Unity
- Digital Twin & 3D Reconstruction
- ML & LLM Model Development & Fine tuning

CERTIFICATIONS

- ML & LLM Model Development & Fine tuning Microsoft Azure
- Machine Learning Engineer Professional Certificate Google Cloud
- Google Introduction to LLM

Completed various courses in udemy, coursera in various domains

CERTIFICATIONS



Sreejith-SHR



Sreejith_SHR



SreejithSHR

WORK EXPERIENCE

Technical Operations Director, Envidox Solutions Jan 2024 -

Responsible For Creation and Deployment of SAAS Products and Technical Current

Lead to WebXR & AR/VR Services And Lead developer in Envichat

Sept 2022 - jul 2024 3D Generalist & Trainer(Internship), House of Metazord-Kgisl Skill

1 year 10 months & Innovations

Digital twin, VR interaction, VR and AR development for Realtime applications .

jul 2023 - Nov 2023 AR/VR Developer(Internship), Machenn innovations

3 months AR Application Development, App buildibg, interactive experiences

Feb 2022 - Aug 2022 3D Graphic Designer (Internship), ApretureWorks

Creating 3D content and Backdrops for educational resources and medias. 6 months

Oct2021 - Apr 2022 3D Modelling and Technical assistant (Internship), Novitech R&D

> A virtual e-commerce platform for cloth traders to connect virtually with their customers

EDUCATION

2020-2024

6 months

B.tech Artificial Intelligence and Data science, KGiSL Instituite of Technology

2018-2020

HSC, Suburban Matric Higher secondary school

2018

SSLC, Suburban Matric Higher secondary school

ACHIEVEMENTS

Virtual Assistant for realtime multi-Tasking, Second place in HACKGENIUS By Eshikhya, KGiSL-2020.

SIGNORA- A Multi performance compatible safety device for women, First Place in D-CIPHER, Women's Day hackathon by KGiSL-2021.

Al based motion capture system - Second place in Oneyes Grand Hackathon by Oneyes infotech - 2023

Intrusion Detection and alertion system for business organization, Third place In BIT-V PRAYUKTHI by BIT 2023

PROJECTS

- Al Based Motion Capture System
- Realtime Object Detection Using OpenCV
- Realtime Pose Estimation
- Thermal Image Processing
- Gait Detection And Analysis
- Web Virtual Tour 360 Service
- Photogrammetry Application For Virtual Servers
- Digital Twin
- 3D Reconstruction
- ML bot TEXT TO IMAGE
- Virtual Try-on SnapAR
- Single image 3D Dept analyser and Creator
- AR Application for Virtual Therapy SnapAR
- First-Person Shooter Game-Unreal Engine
- Web AR Experiences
- AR Guided Application for machines
- Oculus application Unreal & Unity
- Generative AI model Fine tuning
- LLM Based ChatBots & Applications
- Nextjs Task Scheduling Platform
- Many Nextjs and Vuejs Applications and Website
- VR Architecture Application

FREELANCE PROJECT - ENVIDOX SOLUTIONS

EnviChat

A No-code Drag & Drop Chatbot Builder that is used to Create custom and Al based business chatbots in minutes